Guide to the Faculty Newsletter Records, 1991-1994 UA.27.01.0007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Faculty Newsletter records
1991-1994
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Office of Public Affairs & Government Relations
Duke University. Office of Public Affairs & Government Relations. Faculty Newsletter
UA.27.01.0007
0.25 Linear Feet
Papers related to the publication of the Duke Faculty Newsletter in Duke Dialogue, 1991-1994.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Historical note
The Duke Faculty Newsletter was distributed as a stand-alone publication from 1979 to 1986. Post-1986, the newsletter was published as an insert within the campus publication Duke Dialogue. Editorially independent, the newsletter received its funding from the Office of Public Affairs and Government Relations.
Collection Overview
The collection contains news clippings from local publications covering the newsletter, proposed articles, correspondence, and a readership survey.
Provenance
The Faculty Newsletter Records were received by the Duke University Archives as a transfer in July 2013.
Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University. Office of Public Affairs & Government Relations; Duke University. Office of Public Affairs & Government Relations. Faculty Newsletter
- Faculty Newsletter records, 1991-1994
  - Faculty Newsletter in the News, 1993 January-February (Box 1)
  - Duke Dialogue working papers, 1991 September-November (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 1)
  - September Article Clippings, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1993 March (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Article Clippings, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Proposed Aricle, 1993 December (Box 1)
  - Proposed Articles, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Proposed Articles, Correspondence, Reafership Survey, 1992-1994 (Box 1)
  - News Contributions, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Article Clipping, 1992-1993 (Box 1)